

DURGA PANDA

W E B D E V E L O P E R D A T A A N A L Y S T

9535426798

durgaprasadpan@gmail.com

Bangalore, India

durgapanda@github.io/portfolio

TECH SKILLS

- Front End (HTML, CSS, JS, Angular)
- Back End (NodeJs, ExpressJs)
- Database (MongoDB, MySQL)
- CMS (Strapi)
- BI Tools (Power BI)
- Cloud (AWS Certified)
- Microsoft Power Platform
- UI (Photoshop)
- Prototyping tools (Figma, Adobe XD)

SOFT SKILLS

- Project Management
- · People management
- · Stakeholder management
- Effective Communication
- Analytical Thinking

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

JNTU Hyderabad 2006 - 2010

PROFILE

A motivated professional web developer and data analyst with specialist expertise in web development, data analysis and project management. A strategic and agile thinker known for driving change by tackling ambiguous problems and effectively communicating solutions.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER & DATA ANALYST

Fidelity Investments

2019 - Present

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Educational institutions and online classroom management
- •
- •

WEB DEVELOPER

Fidelity Investments

2011 - 2019

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Educational institutions and online classroom management